Eddie Woods papers, circa 1957-2009 M1386
Dept. of Special Collections & University Archives
- Series 7: Jenny Brookes
  - Tsumani of Love: Introduction Track for Tsumani CD and a Review (Box 70, Folder 10)
  - Drawings by Jenny Brookes (Box 70, Folder 11)
  - Jenny Brookes and Poppy Brookes: Photograph (Box 70, Folder 12)
  - Magazine Reproduction of Painting of Jenny by Arnold E. Brookes (Box 70, Folder 13)
  - Eddie Woods to Jenny Brookes: Correspondence (Photocopies July 6, 1980 - August 31, 1999) (Box 70, Folder 14)
  - Eddie Woods to Jenny Brookes: Correspondence (Photocopies November 1999 - July 12, 2007) (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - Jenny Brookes: Drawings (1980s) (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Jenny Brookes Collage to Eddie Woods and Children's Drawings (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - Photographs of Jenny Brookes and Signed Copy of Tsunami of Love (and CD) (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - Eddie Woods' Handwritten Diary While Staying in Devon (May 14th - June 2, 1998) (Box 71, Folder 5)
- Series 8: Unsolicited Manuscripts
  - Katz, Edith Fern: Unsolicited Manuscript (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous Unsolicited Manuscripts and Correspondence (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - Unknown Authors (Box 64, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous Unsolicited Manuscripts and Correspondence (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous Unsolicited Manuscripts and Correspondence (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous Unsolicited Manuscripts and Correspondence (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous Unsolicited Manuscripts and Correspondence (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous Unsolicited Manuscripts and Correspondence (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous Unsolicited Manuscripts and Correspondence (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous Unsolicited Manuscripts and Correspondence (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous Unsolicited Manuscripts and Correspondence (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous Unsolicited Manuscripts and Correspondence (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous Unsolicited Manuscripts and Correspondence (Box 66, Folder 6)
  - Gilet, David: Unsolicited Manuscripts and Correspondence (Box 66, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous Unsolicited Manuscripts and Correspondence (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - Shaffer, Butler: Calculated Chaos: The Institutional Causes of Social Conflict (Unsolicited Manuscript) (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - Taranto, Jim: Naked Apple (Unsolicited Manuscript) (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - Sandy, Tony: That's the Way the Cookie Crumbles - Of Death of a Chip (Unsolicited Manuscript) (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous Unsolicited Manuscripts and Correspondence (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - Adams, Betsy: Unsolicited Manuscripts (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - Lever, Bernice A.: Unsolicited Manuscripts (Box 67, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous Unsolicited Manuscripts and Correspondence (Box 67, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous Unsolicited Manuscripts and Correspondence (Box 67, Folder 8)
  - Westlake, W. Kaumualii: Unsolicited Manuscripts (Box 67, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous Unsolicited Manuscripts and Correspondence (Box 67, Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous Unsolicited Manuscripts and Correspondence (Box 67, Folder 11)
- Series 9: Audiovisual Materials
  This series contains audio and video tapes featuring readings by Beat writers and avant-gardists such as Allen Ginsberg, William Burroughs, Jack Micheline, Ira Cohen, and William Levy. It also contains audio cassette recordings from Ins and Outs' answering machine, International Cannabis Alliance for Reform (I.C.A.R.), and Jenny Brookes and Eddie Woods.
  - Answering Machine Messages
    - Last Message September 9, 1985 (Card-box 73, Audiocassette 1)
    - Last Message September 9, 1985 (Duplicate) (Card-box 73, Audiocassette 1)
    - September 6, 1985 - April 29, 1986 (Card-box 73, Audiocassette 2)
    - September 6, 1985 - April 29, 1986 (Duplicate) (Card-box 73, Audiocassette 2)
    - April 30, 1986 - September 6, 1986 (Card-box 73, Audiocassette 3)
    - April 30, 1986 - September 6, 1986 (Duplicate) (Card-box 73, Audiocassette 3)
    - September 7, 1986 - January 23, 1987 (Card-box 73, Audiocassette 4)
    - September 7, 1986 - January 23, 1987 (Duplicate) (Card-box 73, Audiocassette 4)
    - January 24, 1987 - June 18, 1987 (Card-box 73, Audiocassette 5)
    - January 24, 1987 - June 18, 1987 (Duplicate) (Card-box 73, Audiocassette 5)
    - June 19, 1987 - August 20, 1987 (Card-box 73, Audiocassette 6)
    - June 19, 1987 - August 20, 1987 (Duplicate) (Card-box 73, Audiocassette 6)
    - August 21, 1987 - November 24, 1987 (Duplicate) (Card-box 73, Audiocassette 7)
    - November 25, 1987 - March 1, 1988 (Card-box 73, Audiocassette 8)
    - November 25, 1987 - March 1, 1988 (Duplicate) (Card-box 73, Audiocassette 8)
    - March 3, 1988 - May 29, 1988 (Card-box 73, Audiocassette 9)
    - March 3, 1988 - May 29, 1988 (Duplicate) (Card-box 73, Audiocassette 9)
    - May 30, 1988 - September 3, 1988 (Card-box 73, Audiocassette 10)
    - May 30, 1988 - September 3, 1988 (Duplicate) (Card-box 73, Audiocassette 10)
    - September 3, 1988 - October 20, 1988 (Card-box 73, Audiocassette 11)
    - September 3, 1988 - October 20, 1988 (Duplicate) (Card-box 73, Audiocassette 11)
    - January 1, 1989 - April 3, 1989 (Card-box 73, Audiocassette 12)
    - April 4, 1989 - February 12, 1990 (Card-box 73, Audiocassette 13)
    - February 12, 1990 - July 5, 1990 (Card-box 73, Audiocassette 14)
    - July 5, 1990 - November 7, 1990 (Card-box 73, Audiocassette 15)
    - November 7, 1990 - March 1991 (Card-box 73, Audiocassette 16)
    - March 17, 1991 - March 5, 1992 (Card-box 73, Audiocassette 17)
    - Woof's Greatest Hits: Woof's Answering Machine Messages (Card-box 73)
    - Snuffie Memorial Answering Machine Messages 1987 (Card-box 73)
  - Miscellaneous Cassettes
    - Bloody Mary Definitive (Card-box 74)
    - Jack Micheline in Amsterdam (Card-box 74)
    - Harold Norse of Course (Card-box 74)
    - Eddie Woods Reading at Melweg/Bloody Mary Dealer Like You (Card-box 74)
    - Poesie Als Wapen (Poetry As a Weapon): Eddie Woods and Hans Plomp (Card-box 74)
    - Max Scherr Interview Parts 1 and 2 (Card-box 74)
    - Max Scherr Interview Parts 3 and 4 (Card-box 74)
    - Jack Micheline Interview, 1982 (Card-box 74)
    - McClure on Mushrooms: Eddie Woods Interview with Michael McClure (Card-box 74)
    - Co-Mizery Cafe San Francisco: David Moe and Eddie Woods (Card-box 74)
    - Co-Mizery Cafe San Francisco: Moe and Woods Open Reading September 20, 1980 (Card-box 74)
    - Ira Cohen Reads with Liliana Dlaboha, New York January 15, 1989 (Card-box 74)
    - Ira Cohen Readnig at Visible Voice Part I (Card-box 74)
    - Ira Cohen in Amsterdam and Part 2 Ganga in Hardwar (Card-box 74)
    - Ira Cohen and Janine Pommy-Vega Reading at Ins and Outs, September 20, 1980 (Card-box 74)
    - Green Earth Cloud House Lecture (Card-box 74)
    - Dr. Doo-Wop Show, December 4, 1987 (Card-box 74)
    - Bill Levy/Wordsworth Special FM 100, December 9, 1987 Part I (Card-box 74)
    - Bill Levy/Wordworth Special FM 100, December 9, 1987 Part II (Card-box 74)
    - Coming Out-Joke (Card-box 74)
    - Water Mirror, Louise Landes-Levi/Boa and Baba (Card-box 74)
    - Bill Levy FM 100/Radio Rabotnik, New Year's Eve 1987 #1 (Card-box 74)
    - Bill Levy FM 100/Radio Rabotnik, New Year's Eve 1987 #2 (Card-box 74)
    - Dr. Doo-Wop (Eddie, My Love) 1st Anniversary, March 25, 1988 FM 100 (Card-box 74)
    - Sex and Doo-Wop Bill Levy (June 10, 1988) FM 100 (Card-box 74)
    - Dr. Doo-Wop Tuesday Weld Special, May 19, 1989 (Card-box 74)
    - Dr. Doo-Wop May 26, 1989 (Card-box 74)
    - Dr. Doo Wop Surfing Special/Eddie Your Dedication is Coming Up/Pledging My Love/Gooseface for Baby Cham, February 2, 1992 (Card-box 74)
    - Bill Levy/Radio Rabotnik What Are Words Worth?, July 10, 1987 #I (Card-box 74)
    - Bill Levy/Radio Rabotnik What Are Words Worth?, July 10, 1987 #2 (Card-box 74)
    - Brion Gysin Interview (Card-box 74)
    - Anselm Hollo, With Ruth in Mind (Card-box 74)
    - Tony Van Der Veen Private Poetry Reading October 9, 1990 (Card-box 74)
    - Ins and Outs Benefit Evening Grand Piano, Haight, San Francisco #1 and 2, 1980 (Card-box 74)
    - Ins and Outs Benefit Evening Grand Piano, Haight, San Francisco #3 and 4, 1980 (Card-box 74)
    - Cafe van Dale (Nijmegen) with Eddie Woods, Fifi L'Amour, Mignon Omoroka [Mignon van Ingen], Oct 9,1993 (Card-box 74)
    - Levy-Rabotnik, 11/24/1987 #II (Card-box 74)
    - Flux Interview, November 7, 1991 1 and 2 (Card-box 74)
    - Flux Interview, November 7, 1991 3 and 4 (Card-box 74)
    - H. Blunt - Squatting in A'dam (Card-box 74)
    - Dr. Doo-Wop Cocksucker's Ball, February 21, 1992 (Card-box 74)
    - Dr. Doo-Wop Bill Levy/Rabotnik (with Woof and Miles), July 17, 1987 (Card-box 74)
    - Bill Levy/Miles, August 27, 1987 (Card-box 74)
    - Radio Rabotnik (with Huncke Announcement), October 27, 1987 (Card-box 74)
    - Radio Rabotnik, October 27, 1987 II (Card-box 74)
    - Dr. Doo-Wop Levy, October 30, 1987 (Card-box 74)
    - Dr. Doo-Wop Levy, October 30, 1987 (Card-box 74)
    - Levy - Rabotnik, November 24, 1987/Huncke Excerpt (Card-box 74)
    - Kaufman-Micheline-Winans, Neighborhood Arts Reading, 1975 (Card-box 74)
    - Mel Clay on 'Frisco Radio (Card-box 74)
    - Jack Micheline, Boulder Classic (Card-box 74)
    - North of Manhattan Reading Art Institute January 2, 1977 and Lower Depths (Card-box 74)
    - Rozmari (Card-box 74)
    - Joke - Born That Way (Card-box 74)
    - Simon Vickenoog in A Finch's Eye (Card-box 74)
    - Kaufman T.V., Voix Bulgares - Bob Kaufmans Poetry - T.V. Special (Card-box 74)
    - Better Off Without You, Disconnected (Card-box 74)
    - Starvin Marvin (Card-box 74)
    - Cloud Recording (Card-box 74)
    - Allen Ginsberg - 1st Blues (Card-box 75)
    - The Door: Selected Poems, Robert Creeley (Card-box 75)
    - Gary Snyder, There Is No Other Life: Selected Poems S Press (Card-box 75)
    - John Cage Talking To Hans G Helms On Music and Politics (Card-box 75)
    - The Brion Gysin Show Where Is That Word? (Card-box 75)
    - Edward Dorn Gunslinger Part 1 (Books I & II, The Cycle) (Card-box 75)
    - Allen Ginsberg LIVE at St. Mark's, New York City (Card-box 75)
    - Allen Ginsberg, A Little Bit of Awareness (Card-box 75)
    - Ernst Jandl 13 Radio-Phone Texte (Card-box 75)
    - Wm S. Burroughs Excertps from Naked Lunch & Nova Express S Press (Card-box 75)
    - John Cage Speaks Mureau Mureau Mureau (Card-box 75)
    - Clark Coolidge Polaroid S Press (Card-box 75)
    - Johnny Guitar by John Giorno Stereo (Card-box 75)
    - 55 Anne Waldman (Card-box 75)
    - Derschau Live in Wuppertal (Card-box 75)
    - Jerome Rothenberg Horse-Songs & Other Soundings (Card-box 75)
    - Patty Smith Koeln Reading (Card-box 75)
    - Nicolaus Einhorn Arbeiten (Card-box 75)
    - Raoul Hausmann Poemes Phonetiques Completes (Card-box 75)
    - Alfred Miersch, Lauter Helden (Card-box 75)
    - Jack Micheline, Kerouac in the Spirit M.V.P. Boulder 1982 (Card-box 73)
  - International Cannabis Alliance for Reform (I.C.A.R.)
    - First Conference Session (Card-box 72, Audiocassette A)
    - First Conference Session (Duplicate) (Card-box 72, Audiocassette A)
    - History and Philosophy of Cannabis Criminalisation (Card-box 72, Audiocassette B)
    - History and Philosophy of Cannabis Criminalisation (Duplicate) (Card-box 72, Audiocassette B)
    - Continuation from Tape B, followed by Cannabis Prisoners Abroad (Card-box 72, Audiocassette C)
    - Continuation from Tape B, followed by Cannabis Prisoners Abroad (Duplicate) (Card-box 72, Audiocassette C)
    - Medical Use of Cannabis (i) (Card-box 72, Audiocassette D)
    - Medical Use of Cannabis (i) (Duplicate) (Card-box 72, Audiocassette D)
    - Medical Use of Cannabis (ii) (Card-box 72, Audiocassette E)
    - Medical Use of Cannabis (ii) (Duplicate) (Card-box 72, Audiocassette E)
    - Medical Use of Cannabis (iii) (Card-box 72, Audiocassette F)
    - Medical Use of Cannabis (iii) (Duplicate) (Card-box 72, Audiocassette F)
    - Cannabis Politics Around the World (i) (Card-box 72, Audiocassette G)
    - Cannabis Politics Around the World (i) (Duplicate) (Card-box 72, Audiocassette G)
    - Cannabis Politics Around the World (ii) (Card-box 72, Audiocassette H)
    - Cannabis Politics Around the World (ii) Duplicate (Card-box 72, Audiocassette H)
    - Cannabis Politics Around the World (v) (Card-box 72, Audiocassette L)
    - Cannabis Politics Around the World (v) (Duplicate) (Card-box 72, Audiocassette L)
    - Final Conference Session: Motions, Votes, Future (Card-box 72, Audiocassette M)
    - Final Conference Session: Motions, Votes, Future (Duplicate) (Card-box 72, Audiocassette M)
    - Final Evening I.C.A.R. Conference (Amsterdam/Feb 1980) (Card-box 72)
    - Workshop: Direct Action & Civil Disobedience (Card-box 72, Audiocassette W1)
    - Workshop: Direct Action & Civil Disobedience (Duplicate) (Card-box 72, Audiocassette W1)
    - Workshop: Cannabis & the Media (Card-box 72, Audiocassette W2)
    - Workshop: Cannabis & the Media (Duplicate) (Card-box 72, Audiocassette W2)
    - Workshop: Cannabis Magazines (Card-box 72, Audiocassette W3)
    - Workshop: Cannabis Magazines (Duplicate) (Card-box 72, Audiocassette W3)
    - Workshop: Cannabis & the Law (i) (Card-box 72, Audiocassette W4)
    - Workshop: Cannabis & the Law (i) (Duplicate) (Card-box 72, Audiocassette W4)
    - Workshop: Cannabis & the Law (ii) (Card-box 72, Audiocassette W5)
    - Workshop: Cannabis & the Law (ii) (Duplicate) (Card-box 72, Audiocassette W5)
    - Workshop: Cannabis & the Law (iii) (Card-box 72, Audiocassette W6)
    - Workshop: Cannabis & the Law (iii) (Duplicate) (Card-box 72, Audiocassette W6)
    - Workshop: Direct Action in Action (i) (Card-box 72, Audiocassette W7)
    - Workshop: Direct Action in Action (i) (Duplicate) (Card-box 72, Audiocassette W7)
    - Workshop: Direct Action in Action (ii) (Card-box 72, Audiocassette W8)
    - Workshop: Direct Action in Action (ii) (Duplicate) (Card-box 72, Audiocassette W8)
    - Workshop: Direct Action in Action (iii) (Card-box 72, Audiocassette W9)
    - Workshop: Direct Action in Action (iii) (Duplicate) (Card-box 72, Audiocassette W9)
    - Workshop: Cannabis Cultivation (i) (Card-box 72, Audiocassette W10)
    - Workshop: Cannabis Cultivation (i) (Duplicate) (Card-box 72, Audiocassette W10)
    - Workshop: Cannabis Cultivation (ii) (Card-box 72, Audiocassette W11)
    - Workshop: Cannabis Cultivation (ii) (Duplicate) (Card-box 72, Audiocassette W11)
    - Workshop: Cannabis and Culture (Card-box 72, Audiocassette W12)
    - Workshop: Cannabis and Culture (Duplicate) (Card-box 72, Audiocassette W12)
    - Workshop: Cannabis and Culture (Duplicate) (Card-box 72, Audiocassette W12)
  - Jenny Brookes and Eddie Woods' Audio Cassettes
    - Eddie's Tape Recorded Easter Day '98 With Love XXXX (Card-box 73)
    - Eddie's Tape: A Selection (Card-box 73)
    - For Eddie With Love (Card-box 73)
    - Medley Tape For Jenny, March 28, 1998 (Card-box 73)
    - A'Dam - Devon Cassette Express (Card-box 73)
    - Jenny Telephone, March 28, 1990 and December 12, 1987 (Card-box 73)
  - Video
    - Eddie Woods, Winston March 20, 2000 (Box 81)
    - Luc Sala Interviews Eddie Woods Regarding Allen Ginsberg, 1997 (Box 81)
    - Co Meyer - Woods (Box 81)
    - Bananas, by Eddie Woods (Box 81)
    - Allen Ginsberg Memorial, 1997 (Box 81)
    - Unholy Trinity September 15, 1997 (Box 81)
    - Copy of Five Poets in Amsterdam (DVCAM for HDV Tape) (Box 81)
    - Eddie Woods et al Co Meyer (Box 81)
    - A Tribute to William S. Burroughs (Box 81)
    - Adirondacks and Newport Jazz Festival, Summer 1960 (on 8MM film) (Box 81)
    - Eddie Woods Ruigoord Reading, April 22, 2001 (Box 81)
    - Five Poets in Amsterdam, October 1978 (Master Edit) (Box 82)
    - A Poet of Sound - A Poet of the Cities, Jack Micheline, April 20, 1985 (Box 82)
    - Jack Micheline Soma Cafe, June 12, 1984 (Box 82)
- Series 10: Restricted indefinitely
  - Jenny Brookes erotic photographs (Half-box 93)